{
    "subject": "resource/Miracle_(Cascada_song)",
    "predicate": "property/accessdate",
    "object": "2011-08-28",
    "human_readable": "The access date of the song 'Miracle' by Cascada is August 28, 2011.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9517151713371277,
            "question": "What is the access date of the Cascada song 'Miracle'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9427500367164612,
            "question": "Is August 28, 2011, a relevant date for understanding the song 'Miracle'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9368310570716858,
            "question": "August 28, 2011, refers to the access date of which song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.927068829536438,
            "question": "When was the song 'Miracle' by Cascada accessed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9250178933143616,
            "question": "What is the name of the song with an access date of August 28, 2011?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.842957079410553,
            "question": "On what date was the song 'Miracle' accessed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6254507303237915,
            "question": "Can you think of other songs that might have been popular around August 28, 2011?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6204001307487488,
            "question": "What can you infer about the popularity or usage of the song 'Miracle' based on its access date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5067473649978638,
            "question": "How does knowing the access date of a song like 'Miracle' contribute to our understanding of music consumption patterns?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4459571838378906,
            "question": "Who performed the song 'Miracle'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The access date of the song 'Miracle' by Cascada is August 28, 2011.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2196_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does knowing the access date of a song like 'Miracle' contribute to our understanding of music consumption patterns?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2196_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you infer about the popularity or usage of the song 'Miracle' based on its access date?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2196_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of other songs that might have been popular around August 28, 2011?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2196_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2196_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "The provided text does not mention any information about the song \"Miracle\" by Cascada or its access date.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**\n\nThe access date of a song being unlocked as part of an EXTRA STAGE event, such as roppongi EVOLVED, may be included in the game's metadata or documentation. \n\nSince October 6th, 2010, remixes have been playable by AAAing the original version of the corresponding song. It does not matter what difficulty you do the song in; you can even use BEGINNER or EDIT data. The song will then become available in the next stage for play.\n\nThe access date of a particular song being unlocked as part of an EXTRA STAGE event, such as KIMONO\u2665PRINCESS or Replicant D-action, may be included in the game's metadata or documentation, and can be accessed on certain dates."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": " The information provided does not indicate the access date for the song 'Miracle' by Cascada."
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"no\"}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "No"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The song 'Miracle' by Cascada does not appear in the provided context information.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on BEMANI games and their songs, with no mention of Cascada or the song \"Miracle\".",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of the song \"Miracle\" by Cascada or its access date in the provided context information, which makes it unlikely to be correct.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}